

ROBIN RAJ SB

Programmer, UI Designer

Objective

To expand my knowledge and also be a part of a firm where i can improve myself and also enhance my abilities as a programmer and designer.

DOB: 13-17-1995

Contact

Address:

Robin House, Mevalloor Karyavattom PO Thiruvananthapuram Pin : 695581

Phone:

+ 91 7736185778

Fmail[.]

robinrajsb@gmail.com

Profiles

Website

robinrajsb.github.io

Social

/robin.raj.sb

in /robinrajsb

✓ @RobinRaj_SB

/RobinRajSB_Tech

ABOUT ME

I am Robin, designer specialized in creating beautiful, yet functional websites and digital interfaces, also a programmer at heart, I dedicate most of my time improving my designing skills and learning about new technologies. I'm a very passionate designer that's always wanting to grow, learn and try something new. I love what I do and I work exceptionally hard with who I work with.

EDUCATION

2014 - Present St. Thomas Institute for Science And Technology

B.Tech Computer Science and Engineering

currently in S8

2012 - 2014 St. Johns Model HSS, Nalanchira

XII Computer Science
Percentage: 68.3%

2012 St.Mary's Higher Secondary School, Pattom

SSLC

Percentage: 92%

EXPERIENCES

Jan 2018 - Current Creative Team, YASYA 2018

YASYA is a national level inter-college cultural and technical fest of St.Thomas Institute for Science and technology, Trivandrum

Creative Assistant and Video Editor

Logo Designer, YASYA 2018

VFX, Post-production, YASYA Promo Video 2018

Jul 2014 - Current Multimedia Team, STIST

Jan 2018 - Current STIST College Magazine 2017-18

Sub Designer

PROJECTS

2017 - Current Self-Driving Car using Machine Learning

Self-Driving Car which can avoid obstacles, respond to traffic light, stop sign, pedestrian detection and overtaking other vehicles on the track. It has a Raspberry Pi 3 Single boad Computer which acts as a client to send video data(Pi Camera) and Distance Data(Ultrasonic Sensor) to the server. The Server consists of a powerfull computer which runs a Neural Network for Steering Predection and Haar-Cascade Classifiers for traffic light and stop sign detection. It uses Supervised Machine Learning, that is the car is trained on a track and generate a model based on the training data.

model based on the training data.

Sept - Nov 2016 MininProject - Placement Cell Management System

Designed and developed a Placement Cell Management System using Netbeans and MySQL as a part of the cource syllabus. It helped in real-time management of data from Companies, Colleges and Student Database.



ROBIN RAJ SB

Programmer, UI Designer

Objective

To expand my knowledge and also be a part of a firm where i can improve myself and also enhance my abilities as a programmer and designer.

DOB: 13-17-1995

Contact

Address:

Robin House, Mevalloor Karyavattom PO Thiruvananthapuram Pin: 695581

Phone:

+917736185778

Email:

robinrajsb@gmail.com

Profiles

Website

robinrajsb.github.io

Social

f /robin.raj.sb



🏏 @RobinRaj_SB

/RobinRajSB_Tech

SKILLS

Design

C C++ Java

Programming Python

WebDesign(HTML,CSS,Javascript)

MySQL Arduino

Android App development(Android Studio) **Application Development**

App development using Xamarin

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe Xd Adobe Indesign InkScape

Adobe AfterEffects Adobe Premere pro **Video Production** Camtasia Studio

Sony Vegas Pro

Boards Arduino and Raspberry Pi

Entrepreneurship Other Skills

Knowledge in Computer Hardware

ACHIEVEMENTS AND OTHER ACTIVITIES

Participated in Sixth Sense Robotics workshop conducted by IIT-DELHI as a part of their annual 2017

'Techno Management Festival' TRYST-2017 of

IIT Delhi.

Participated in Artificial Intelligence & Machine Learning

workshop conducted by National Student's Space Challenge-IIT Kharagpur at RIET, TVM as a part of their

annual 'Techno Fest' ITIHA2K18.

Owns a Youtube Channel named "Robin Raj SB" for tech 2012 - Current

reviews, Motion Graphics, Tutorials etc.

DECLARATION

2018

I hereby certify that the above statements are true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

Robin Raj SB